Jenny: Hello?
Rob: Hi, Jennifer?
Jenny: Yes.
Rob: This is Rob Walker from London 24Seven.
I’m phoning to check you got the email I sent you.
Jenny: Er, what was it about?
Rob: It was the information about your hotel for next week.
Jenny: Just a second.
Yes, here it is.
Hotel Indigo, London Street.
Where is it exactly?
Rob: It’s very near Paddington Station.
You can get the Heathrow Express train from the airport to the station.
It only takes about 15 minutes.
Jenny: Great.
Can I walk to the hotel from the station?
Rob: Yes, it’s very near.
Can you see it on the map?
Jenny: Er… yes, I have it now.
Rob: Turn left when you leave the station.
Then go straight on for a bit and turn right into London Street.
The hotel’s opposite Norfolk Square.
Jenny: Great.
Rob: I can come to the hotel in the morning on your first day.
We can walk to the office together.
Jenny: OK. See you then.
Rob: Bye.
Jenny: Bye.